在这个星期天
On this sunday
在我们进行初选
before the primary
去为我们的社区候选人投票前
When we will go to the polls to exercise our blessed franchise,
我们来回顾一下出埃及记第18章
Our lesson comes from exodus, chapter 18.
第二天
"And it came to pass on the morrow
摩西坐着审判百姓
"That moses sat to judge the people:
百姓从早到晚
"And the people stood by him
都站在摩西的左右
"From the morning unto the evening.
摩西独自审判百姓
"And moses judged the people.
独自承受这一切重负
"And he shouldered this tremendous burden all alone.
有一天 摩西的岳父对他说
"And one day, his father-In-Law said to him,
摩西 为什么你要
"'Moses, why do you carry this
独自承担重担
"Awesome responsibility by yourself?
你需要有才能的人帮你
"You need other wise men to help you rule
审判百姓
"Justly over the people.'
摩西听从他岳父的话
"So moses hearkened to the voice of his father-In-Law,
挑选有才能的人来审判百姓
"And chose able men to rule over the people."
你们说有道理吗?
Can i preach it like i feel it?
在这周二
This tuesday,
当我们选择
When we choose the men and women
领导我们城市的人时
Who will lead our city,
我们必须把这些标准谨记心中
We would do well to keep those standards in mind.
诚信之人
Men of truth,
敬畏上帝
Who fear god
憎恶贪婪
and hate covetousness.
哈里路亚!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
愿主保佑你
God bless you.
见到你真好
Good to see you.
- 你好吗? - 还不错
- How you doing? - Just fine.
妈妈最近如何? 帮我带个好
How's mama? Tell her i said hello.
- 团契委员会将在2点钟开始 - 如果我迟到了...
- Fellowship committee at 2:00: - If i'm late...
- 我们会等你 - 好吧
- We'll wait. - All right.
谢谢你们前来 孩子们
Thank you for coming, young man, young lady.
- 牧师 - 市议员
- Reverend. - Councilman.
Carcetti夫人 最近可好?
Mrs. Carcetti. How are you?
谢谢你邀请我们
Thank you so much for having us.
- 谢谢 - 你的讲道很有趣
- Thank you. - Lnteresting sermon.
民调显示你有机会
Polls seem to think you have a chance.
我们仍在错误的边缘
Well, we're within the margin of error.
错误的边缘 这个词组很有意思
Margin of error. That's an interesting phrase.
我看到州代表Watkins也站在你这边
And i see you've got delegate watkins working the crowd.
我希望他不是唯一的一个
Well, i'm hoping he's not going to be the only one.
我想说的是 市议员先生
I'll tell you what, councilman.
在周二投票前 我会保持开放的心态
I will keep an open mind until i walk into that booth on tuesday.
- 如果你赢了-- - 你太看得起我了
- And if you win-- - You're holding me to a high standard.
- 摩西? 我的上帝 牧师... - Tommy
- Moses? I mean, jesus, reverend... - Tommy.
- 很抱歉 我不该说这些话 - 摩西只适用于现在
- I'm sorry. I can't believe i said that. - Moses will do for now.
第二阶段我们再请上帝来帮忙
We'll save jesus for your second term.
- 祝你愉快 谢谢你们前来 - 谢谢你
- Have a good one now. Thank you all so much for coming. - Thank you. ??
火线重案组 第四季 第6集
The.Wire.S04E06
* When you walk through the garden *
* you gotta watch your back *
* well I beg your pardon *
* walk the straight and narrow track *
* if you walk with Jesus *
* he's gonna save your soul *
* you gotta keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* he's got the fire and the fury *
* at his command *
* well you don't have to worry *
* if you hold on to Jesus hand *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* when the thunder rolls *
* just gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* you gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* keep the devil *
别自己在家里瞎忙   - Norman Wilson
- 有动静吗? - 连望风的都没有
- Signs o' life? - Not even a lookout.
- 也许他们都去教堂了 - 那可是我们的补货的姑娘啊
- Maybe they went to church. - Our lady of the re-Up.
他早晚会出现的
He'll show up sooner or later.
- 给我电话 - 好的
- Call me. - All right.
请投Carcetti一票
Vote for carcetti.
请在周二投Carcetti一票
Vote for carcetti on tuesday.
Tommy Carcetti竞选市长 谢谢
Tommy carcetti running for mayor. Thanks.
- 你好 市议员 - 早上好
- Hello, councilman. - Good morning.
我一直在留意你的竞选活动 我是教师
I've been following your campaign. I'm a teacher.
- 好极了 - 我教高中生物
- Excellent. - High-School biology.
- 是吗? 在市里? - 在巴尔的摩县 我想说的是
- What? Here in the city? - Baltimore county. I just wanted say
我非常赞同你在学校董事会改革方面的见解
I think your position on school-Boardreform Is very encouraging.
- 那你会投我一票吗? - 如果我住在市里 我肯定会
- So you'd vote for me? - If i lived in the city, i absolutely would.
- 祝你周二好运 - 谢谢你
- Good luck on tuesday. - Thank you.
- 见鬼了都是县里来的 - 没关系 我们这里快结束了
- They're all fucking county people. - We're almost done here anyway.
- Thomas 看这个 - 那是什么?
- Thomas, look at this. - What's that?
看看
Check it out.
Carcetti曾为臭名昭著的恶房东辩护
在你的从业生涯中 你是否代理过一个叫Bobby Harrison的人?
In your private practice, you ever represent a bobby harrison?
恶房东? 干 当然没有 我甚至不记得见过这人
The slumlord? Fuck, no. I don't remember ever even meeting this guy.
"Carcetti成功地撤销了最严重的指控
"Carcetti got the most serious charges dismissed
其他指控的罚金也被降低
"And the others reduced to small fines.
恶房东再一次逍遥法外
"The slumlord once again walked free with a slap on the wrist
而数百名房客不得不继续
"While hundreds of tenants continue to suffer
- 忍受的恶劣的居住条件" - 在最后一刻 他们慌了
- "Substandard living conditions." - Last-Minute smear. They're running scared.
- Royce - 还会是谁?
- Royce. - Who else?
这城市65%的租金都是他的
65% of the city rents.
Bobby Harrison的名声在城里可是非常臭
Bobby harrison's name is dirt in this town.
在选举前两天他们玩这套
Two days before the election and they smear me?
法院台阶上 这照片是什么时候照的?
Courthouse steps. When the fuck was this taken?
- 这是假的 是PS的 - 我们有时间证明吗?
- It's a fake. They photo-Shopped me. - We have time to prove that?
- 我们可以试试 - 试吧 该死 我要被拖后腿了
- We can try. - Try, shit. I'm gonna lose behind this.
冷静点 Tommy  我们早就料到他们最后会出烂招
Easy, tommy. We always figured they'd pull some last-Minute shit.
至少现在我们知道是什么了
At least now we know what it is.
干
Fuck.
你要记得 你可是代表你父亲
I want you to remember, you're representing your daddy.
我知道 不过她为什么要见我们?
Yeah, i know. What she wanna see us for, anyway?
也许她有惊喜要给你 孩子
Maybe she got somethin' special in mind for you, boy.
- 酷 - 她是Barksdale家族成员
- Cool. - She's a barksdale.
她能发现别人的才华
She know talent when she sees it.
而且 他们欠我们家很多
Besides, they owe this family a lot.
你父亲 他帮他们顶了罪
Your daddy, he stood tall for them.
我知道 他是个战士
I know, i know. He a soldier.
- 虎父无犬子 - 毫无疑问
- Like father, like son. - No doubt.
- 几点了? - 3点30
- What time you got? - 3:30.
妈的迟到了
Motherfucker late.
找你的 Marlo
It's for you, marlo.
说吧 什么事
Yeah, speak.
没问题
You on it.
只要她按时到 我们就没问题
As long as she hit her mark, we straight.
我要在什么时候去接那个小妞?
What time i gotta pick up that skinny girl?
好吧
A'ight.
他们说的是几点?
So what time they say?
明天晚上
Tomorrow night.
她会在8:45来自纽约的车上
She be on the 8:45 from new york. Yeah.
- 我们可以搞定 - 不 我去
- We can take care of that. - No. I'll do it.
不想搞砸了
Don't want nothin' to go wrong.
- 你确定? - 是的
- You sure about that? - It's a'ight.
你们可以不用插手
You can hang back on this.
我想我还拍到了这个
Yeah, i think i got this one, too.
Marlo Stanfield
Marlo stanfield.
他也不怎么有脑子
He ain't so much.
还用手机联系
Using cell phones and shit.
他在说什么?
What's he sayin' now?
我要在什么时候去接那个小妞?
"What time i gotta pick up the skinny girl?
我去
"I do it.
不想搞砸了
"Don't want nothing to go wrong."
也许他要去接他女朋友?
Maybe he's picking up a girlfriend?
纽约来的小妞?
"Skinny girl from new york"?
这是暗语 是可卡因
It's code. Cocaine.
该死
Damn.
Marlo亲自去接货
For marlo himself to get near a package...
他是一个白痴 我告诉过你了
He's a mope. I told ya.
- 那我们要怎么做? - 我们进行反击
- So what do we do about it? - We work up some counter lit.
这就是为什么我们这儿有打印机
That's why we have a printer on retainer.
我们最好能查到原始的照片
Best if we run down the original photograph.
如果我们能够证明这张是假的--
If we can prove this one's a fake--
我在太阳报呆了22年可不是白呆的 我有人脉
I didn't work at "sun" papers for 22 damn years Not to know somebody.
我给照片资料室的Paul Mccardle打个电话
I'm gonna call paul mccardle at the photo library.
- 如果我们还是找不到呢? - 那我们自己做一张假照片
- And if we still can't find it? - Then we put out a fake photo of our own.
让Royce在汽车旅馆里和一具女孩尸体 还有一个男孩搞在一起
Show royce in a motel with a dead girl and a live boy.
把屎丢回去没什么用啊 太晚了
We can't sling mud back. Not this late.
放松 我是开玩笑的
Relax. I'm kidding.
你继续按日程走 按原定计划
You get back on your schedule. Hit all your stops.
今晚去和捐助人用餐 表现得友好点
Go to that donors' dinner tonight and make nice.
我们来处理这事
We'll take care of this.
你不能这样对我们
You can't do this to us.
Bey帮你们扛了罪
Bey took the weight for all y'all.
我们也充分补偿过你了
And you've been amply compensated.
- 但是这都过去了 - 对Bey来说没有
- But time moves on. - Not for bey, it don't.
我的意思是 我们已经没有收入了
What i meant to say is there's no more money coming in.
没有生意了
No more business.
Avon不在了 队伍也散了
Avon is gone. So are his people.
该死
Shit.
你倒是还活得挺滋润的
You seem to still be doin' all right for yourself.
我没有什么可以帮你的了
There's nothing more i can do for you.
Bey什么都知道 你忘记了吗?
Bey know everything. You forget that?
那他会怎么做? 他要向谁告发?
And what's he gonna do? Who's he gonna tell?
就算是那样 我为什么要在意?
And what do i care if he does?
Bey从没听过我说过任何关于生意上的事
Bey never heard me say a damn thing about business.
你兄弟呢?
What about your brother?
如果Bey说了什么  Avon可能会在里面呆更长时间
Avon could be gone longer if bey gets to speakin' his mind.
我才不在乎Avon
I couldn't care less about avon.
我要你们俩一起来 是因为我要你们一起听我说的话
The thing is i wanted you both to hear it from me
这样就不会有人被欺骗
So there ain't no lies from here on in.
在过去的两年里 我们给了她够多的钱
She even paid enough over the last two years
你应该有足够的钱生活下去 孩子
That you should have enough money going forward, son.
你父亲并没有被遗忘
Your father has not been disrespected here.
过去的收入都有你们的一份
You both got what was coming.
但是不能这样下去了
But ain't nothing lasts forever.
- 监狱里的告密者? - 昨晚打电话来
- Jailhouse snitch? - Called last overnight.
Worden和他谈过 做笔交易他可以帮我们
Worden talked to him. Says for a deal, he can give us the case.
- 真的假的 - 要起草一份正式文件
- No shit. - Gonna write up a writ,
交到州检察官办公室
Send it over to the state's attorney's office,
让他们明天一大早就签好
Get them to sign off on it first thing tomorrow morning.
- 为什么那么急? - 我们抓紧点的话
- What's the rush? - We jump on this.
可以在选举前搞点大动静出来
We cause a major shit stink right before the election.
如果那家伙真的知道为什么证人 叫什么名字来着?
If this guy really knows why the witness-- What's-His-Name?
- Braddock - --被杀了的话
- Braddock. - --Was killed,
- 也许对市长不是什么好事 - 对那个白小子Carcetti来说可不是坏事
- Might be bad for the mayor. - If it's not bad for the white boy, carcetti.
- 你关心哪一边? - 关心他妹
- You care, either way? - Fuck no.
我两边都不鸟 我根本都不投票
I don't give a shit either way. I don't even vote.
但是给他们搞点麻烦挺有趣的
But it'll be fun to fuck with them downtown suits.
也许能让你上11点的新闻
Maybe get you on the 1 1 :00 news.
好好报复他们一下
Get a little payback for all that shit they put you through.
初选前只剩下两天
With only two days left before the primary,
今天 竞选工作人员通过
Campaign officials traded charges today
散发有争议性的传单
Over a controversial flier distributed
在一些非洲裔美国人社区互相指责
In some african-American neighborhoods.
现任市长的绝对领先优势
What seemed to be a secure lead for the incumbent mayor
在最近几天逐渐消失
Has evaporated in recent days.
最新的太阳报民调显示
The latest "sun"-Wqmd poll
俩人竞争进入白热化状态
Shows the two men in a virtual dead heat
而市议员Tony Gray紧跟其后
With councilman tony gray trailing.
4%的潜在投票者还在摇摆不定
4% of the likely voters are still undecided,
而初选--
And with the prim--
我真想这一切早点结束
I can't wait for it to be over.
我也是
Yeah, me either.
那传单能够伤害你吗?
Can that flier hurt you?
我们在太阳报的文档里发现了原始的照片
You know, we found the original photo In "the sun"'s files.
他们把我的脸嫁接到 某次在法院台阶上的采访照片上
They grafted my puss onto some perp-Walk shot
我站的地方原来是某个副警长
On the courthouse steps. I'm standing where some sheriff's deputy was.
我的上帝 太贱了
Oh my god. What a nasty business.
Royce发誓这事和他无关
Royce is swearing he had nothing to do with it.
他声称是个别人自己搞出来的
Claims it must've been somebody freelancing.
Norman和Terri说不用担心
Well, norman and terri say not to worry.
都是游戏的一部分
It's all in the game.
你知道 如果我落后15个点
You know, when i was 15 points behind,
那我也认了 知道吗
I was resigned, you know?
惨败 我也可以接受
A landslide, i could live with that.
我的意思是 所有人都没指望过什么
I mean, what else did anyone expect, anyway?
白人想在巴尔的摩竞选市长?
White guy runnin' for mayor in baltimore?
但是 搞成这样
But this:
Jen 如果我只落后2个点输掉  这会让我很不好受
Jen, if i lose this here by two points, it's gonna kill me.
这太他妈的难受了
It's gonna just fucking kill me.
你必须要像个男子汉站起来了 Nay
You gonna have to step up now, nay.
- 好的 - 做这个家庭的支柱
- A'ight. - Be the man of the family.
你爸出来混的时候 比你还小
You older than your daddy was when he went out on the corner.
这就是我一直说的 他退学了
That's what i been sayin'. Damn. He quit school.
你不能退学
You ain't quittin' school.
- 现在还不能 - 妈
- Not yet. - Ma.
但是你要靠自己了
But you are goin' out on your own.
你去向Bodie要点货吧
You gonna ask bodie for a package.
- 如果他不答应呢? - 我才不接受拒绝
- What if he say no? - I ain't take no for an answer.
- 刚有了 - 什么意思?
- Just did. - What you mean?
- 在Brianna那里 - 把电话给我
- From brianna. - Hand me the damn phone.
她说已经给你够多钱了是什么意思?
What she say about you already gettin' paid enough money?
她就是个大话精 Namond 知道吗?
She a lyin' bitch, namond. You see?
这世界上还有很多你不了解的东西
There's a lot about this world you just don't know.
说到底她就是知道你不会告密
What it come down to is she know you ain't gonna snitch.
- 不管她说什么狗屎一大堆的 - 她有那个权力
- No matter what shit she pull. - She got that right.
她在利用你 Bey 她在利用你
She takin' advantage of you, bey. She takin' advantage of you.
好像她都算计好了似的
Sound like she got it all figured.
那婊子都算计好了
Bitch got it figured out, all right.
她不打招呼就把我们甩了
She cuttin' us loose without notice. Nothin'.
就像回到家所有东西都被丢在大街上
Like comin' home, findin' our shit in the street, bey.
她根本不鸟你 还有Avon
She don't give a fuck about you, avon, none of it.
她居然有胆这样和我说话
She had the nerve to talk to me on this,
好像她做得很公平
Iike she gonna set things straight
我说的都是真的
So i don't tell no lies.
Jen 很抱歉打扰你 他说他不会睡的
Jen, i'm sorry. He said he'd be up.
他已经去办公室了
He's already gone to the office.
他去那干什么?
Well, what's he doing there?
他睡不着 已经去好几个小时了
He couldn't sleep. He's been there for hours.
该死 晚安
shit. See ya.
因为我们还是缺乏
And given that we still have a shortage of officers
愿意在投票站帮忙的人手
Willing to work secondary at the polling stations,
如果有人有兴趣
We're asking for anyone interested
今天下午可以联系机动组
To contact tactical this afternoon.
下一项内容 新通缉令
Next order of business: fresh warrants,
第一个是被指控谋杀和藏械的
Beginning with murder and weapons charges
Omar Little
On one omar little.
- 有人认识这个帅哥吗? - 当然
- Anyone know this mutt? - Oh, yeah!
- 他杀了谁? - 小店里的某位女士
- Who'd he kill? - Some lady in a store.
- 好象是个普通市民 - 普通市民?
- Reads like a taxpayer. - A taxpayer?
这上面说 他被指控谋杀重罪
From what this says, he's charged with felony homicide,
抢劫过程中杀人
To wit: murder in the commission of a robbery.
那个狗娘养的早该被铐起来了
About fuckin' time someone got some paper on that motherfucker.
不过我们没有固定住址 也不知道他住哪
Anyhow, we got no fixed address, no known abode.
如果抓到他 请联系凶杀组的
But if apprehended, Contact detectives holley
- Holley和Crutchfield警探 - 你想找Omar Little?
- and crutchfield in homicide. - You wanna find omar little?
你去找一个从街角逃跑的
You look for a corner boy running away from a corner
裤子里有屎的流浪男孩就是了
With shit in his pants.
什么时候Omar开始对普通人下手了?
You ever know omar to do a citizen?
把资料传发一下吧
Anyway, pass these around.
- 天啊 Tommy - 我花了几个小时
- Jesus, tommy. - I spent a couple hours
看最新的资料 重新安排日程
Going over the latest data, rearranged the schedule.
Tommy 给你点小提示--
Tommy. A little bit of knowledge--
有好些中产黑人选区
There's a bunch of middle class black precincts
倾向Tony但是还没最终决定
Which are strong on tony but still have a high undecided.
我想我们能够争取一些选票
I think we can pick up some votes--
那些人讨厌市长 你会得到那些选票的
Those people hate the mayor. You're gonna get those votes,
- 如果不是你 就是Gray - 我们今天逐门逐户拜访
- And if you don't, gray will. - We go door to door today.
只要他们不投给Royce就好
As long as they don't go to royce.
如果我要当选 我需要一些黑人选票
I need some black votes if i'm gonna be mayor.
我需要那些社区的支持
I need some kind of mandate from that community.
如果我能赢得一些...
If i sneak in with a bare plurality...
- 我们有可能赢得竞选 - 你以为我整晚都做了什么?
- we might just win this thing. - What do you think kept me up all night?
虽然我很敬佩你那么早起来做分析
With all due respect to your early-Morning analysis,
我们争取到了3次连续的高峰期电台采访机会
We got three back-To-Back drive-Time radio interviews
我可是磨破鞋底才争取来的
I wore out my kneepads to get.
为你工作的这些人是专业人士 Tommy
The people running your campaign are professionals, tommy.
别自己在家里瞎忙
Don't try this shit at home.
你知道吗 也许我能给你搞个什么官做做
You know, there might just be a job for you In a carcetti administration--
新闻发言人 或者幕僚长
Press secretary, chief of staff.
给我滚进那车里
get in the fucking car.
Duquan
Prez先生
Mr. Prez.
- 你能跟我来吗? - 我做错了什么?
- Can you come with me, please? - What'd i do?
早点来 我会让你进来 你可以洗澡
Get here early. I'll let you in, and you can shower.
我的脏衣服怎么办?
My dirty clothes?
把它们放进这个袋子 留在柜子里
Put 'em in this bag, leave 'em in the locker.
我会把它们带回家洗
I'll bring 'em home and wash 'em.
去洗澡吧 你要迟到了
Go ahead and get cleaned up. You'll be late for class.
Paul Monnel
Hey, paul. Hey, monnel.
- 骚货 - 该死 她很正啊
- Skanky ho. - Damn, she good, though.
你说的对
Yeah yeah. You right about that.
嗨 Tiff 宝贝儿 我也有钱
Hey, yo, tiff, baby. I got 50c too.
干你们
Fuck y'all.
三个一起来? 你知道她行的
Damn. All three at once? You know she could.
我知道你行的
I know you could.
- 长官 - 稍息
- Sir. - At ease.
老兄 我讨厌老大们从八楼溜达下来
Man, i hate it when the bosses creep below the eighth floor.
是啊 我要好一会来松开我的绷紧的屁眼
Yeah, well, i need a moment just to unclench my asshole.
- 长官? - Braddock一案的调查
- Sir? - The braddock investigation.
正在做 Norris和Greggs正在弄
It's coming. Norris and greggs are wringing it out.
我他妈当然知道正在做
I fuckin' know it's coming.
Burrell局长今天一大早就来客人了
Commissioner burrell had a visit first thing this morning
州检察官Demper亲自上门拜访
From state's attorney demper himself,
问他为什么在初选前一天
Asking why one day before the primary
我们的警探还在底下搞小动作
Our detectives were trying to writ out a jailhouse snitch.
我们刚好收到风声
The tip came when it did.
我没有督办 也没有压下来
I didn't push it, and i didn't hold it back either.
- 顺其自然 - 没错 长官
- Let the chips fall where they may. - Exactly, sir.
警长? 干你的顺其自然
Sergeant? Fuck your falling chips.
如果Braddock被杀是因为他是证人
If braddock was killed because he was a witness
而我们在初选前一天搞这么一出
And we break the case one day before the primary,
Royce会恨我们一辈子  Royce有可能赢得选举
Royce hates us forever-- And royce might win the election.
如果Braddock被杀是因为其他原因  而我们今天破案了
If braddock was killed for any other reason And we break it today,
那么Carcetti会恨死我们  Carcetti很可能赢得选举
Then carcetti hates our guts-- And carcetti could win.
我明白了
I see your point.
机动组告诉我 我们还缺20个人手
Tactical tells me we're still about 20 bodies short
去维持投票场所秩序
For manning the polling places.
我要你马上安排两个警探
I want you to detail two detectives
去维持选举秩序
To uniformed election duty immediately.
让我猜猜 让Norris和Greggs去
Lemme guess: norris and greggs.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
他们今天下午一点会去机动组报道
They're to report to tactical at 1 300 today For election orientation.
他们可以在周三的时候 继续搞他们的告密的案子
They can pick up their writ And talk to their snitch on wednesday.
美国式民主
American democracy.
让那些第三世界的傻逼见识一下 我们是怎么做事的
Let's show those third-World fucks how it's done.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我有一个好消息给各位
I have what i think is some very good news for all of you.
我们准备在这里实施
We're going to be implementing
马里兰大学试点项目
The university of maryland pilot program.
你只在我班里挑了三个傻货?
You're only taking three of my knuckleheads?
我们会在八年级挑总共十名学生
A total of 10 children from the eighth grade
作为首班学生 八男二女
In this first class-- Eight boys and two girls.
如果事情顺利... 这就会只是个开始
- If things go well... - It's a start.
- 什么时候开始? - 今天早上
- When? - This morning.
哈里路亚 越早越好
Hallelujah. Not a moment too soon.
- 我看起来如何? - 镜头里看起来很棒
- How was l? - Good on steiner.
在早上的脱口秀节目里更棒
Better on the a.M. Talk shows.
我还以为你处理好了那传单的事
I thought you handled that call about the fliers well.
干他娘的Royce
Fucking royce.
如果我因为这狗屎输了...
If i lose because of this bullshit--
你输了我们有的是东西可以抱怨 你赢了也是一样
You lose, we can blame it on 10 different things. Same thing if you win.
猜猜我刚和谁通话了?
Guess who i just got off the phone with?
州参议员Davis 他想和我们见个面
State senator davis. He wants a meet.
Clay Davis?  我干嘛要和那个狗娘养的搞在一起?
Clay davis? Why would i wanna get into bed with that motherfucker?
他并没有明说
He didn't actually come out and say it,
但是听起来他打算跟Watkins的风
But it sounds like he's ready to follow watkins
- 在市长赌局里下筹码 - 他想要什么回报?
- And jump the mayor's ship. - What's he want in return?
和他往常要的一样
Shee-It. Same thing he always wants.
我猜至少要给他最中意的竞选委员会两万捐款
At least 20k to his favorite campaign committee is my guess.
也许要三万 你知道Clay的价码不便宜
Maybe even 30, 'cause you know clay ain't cheap.
政治方面 我可不会承诺他任何东西
Well, i'm not promising him anything policy-Wise.
你认为Clay Davis会鸟什么规矩?
You think clay davis gives a fuck about policy?
只是一场交易
Naw, this is strictly for services rendered.
他也许在忽悠我们
He might be conning us--
拿钱不办事
Taking the money, then sitting on his hands.
也许 但是我们最多就亏点钱
Maybe. But then all we have to lose is money.
但是他也许可以在西区帮点小忙
Could be the extra little push we need on the west side.
- 安排一下会面 - 已经安排好了
- Set it up. - I already did.
- 把分母倒过来 - 倒过来是什么意思?
- Lnvert the denominator-- - What invert mean?
分子和分母调换位置
The numerator and the denominator switch places.
- 上下颠倒 - 你为什么要那么做?
- Turn upside down. - Why you do that?
因为这样行得通 这是公式
Because it works. That's the formula.
打扰一下 Pryzbylewski先生
Excuse me, mr. Pryzbylewski.
Namond Brice Darnell Tyson 还有Zenobia Dawson
Namond brice, darnell tyson and zenobia dawson.
收拾东西跟我们来
Grab your things and come with us, please.
安静 安静
Quiet, quiet.
别闹
Calm down, please.
- 我们做了什么? 我们有麻烦了吗? - 跟我来就好
- What'd we do? We in trouble? - Just come with me.
该死 我怎么总碰到这种事
Shit. It's the story of my life.
- 他们不会回来了 - Prezbo先生 他们被捕了吗?
- They ain't coming back. - Yo, mr. Prezbo, they gettin' arrested?
不...
- No...
Nay 你的XBOX能给我吗?
yo, nay, can i have your xbox?
因为你要去的地方不会需要它了
'Cause you ain't gonna need it where you are.
他们做了什么?
What'd they do?
Markeith Kwame还有Latonya
Markeith, kwame and latonya.
收拾东西跟我们来
Bring your things and come with us.
又来?
Again?
你知道我不能公开挺你  不能在最后关头这个时候
You know i can't publicly endorse you. Not at this late hour.
那我们有什么可以谈的?
Then what are we talking about?
我放手不做我平时在选举日会做的事
I lay back and not do what i usually do on election day.
我看到你们在争取第七和第九区
I see you all get a push In the seventh and ninth districts, say,
也许还有11区 Freemont西边的一部分
And maybe that piece of the 1 1th west of freemont.
我把我手上的选票分点给你们
I split some of my tickets for y'all.
也就是把选民补贴分给你们了
I split my walkaround money.
你知道 礼尚往来嘛
You know, the usual to-And-Fro.
政治是一件好事 我的朋友
Politics is a good thing, pardner.
那是少数派的观点
That's a minority opinion.
我们来点餐吧
Let's order.
我饿得如果你们牵来一头牛 我都可以吃完
I'm hungry enough to eat the horse you rode in on.
如果你不介意
If you don't mind,
我们没多少时间坐下来吃饭了
we're a little busy For a sit-Down lunch.
那当然
Oh, no doubt.
把单买了再走就行
Just leave enough for the tab.
- 她疯了 - 她说你在场
Naw, she crazy. She says you were there.
我不在 而且 那也不算强奸 她自愿的
I wasn't. Besides, it wasn't even rape. She wanted to.
你怎么知道? 你又不在那儿
How do you know? You weren't there.
- 我看见她和他们进去 - 和谁进去?
- I saw her go in with them. - Go in with who?
我现在没时间和你玩 年轻人
This is no time to play, young man.
你现在麻烦大了
You are in very serious trouble.
你看见她和谁进去男更衣室了?
Who did you see her go in the boys' bathroom with?
Paul和Monnel
Paul and monnel.
Paul和Monnel? 那你那时在干吗?
Paul and monnel? And what were you doing?
- 望风 - 那你也有份参与
- Lookout. - So you were involved.
但是我什么都没看见
But i didn't even see what happened.
- 你在帮忙望风 - 不是这样的 听我说
- You were standing guard. - No, listen,
Monnel给了我5元 只是让我站在门口
monnel gave me $5 And just told me to stand by the door
如果有人来就喊
and holler if someone came.
这太不公平了 我什么都没做
This isn't even fair. I didn't even do nothing.
两个八年级男生强奸一个八年级女生时
You stood lookout while two eighth-Grade boys
- 你在望风 - 但是她是自愿的
- Raped an eighth-Grade girl. - But she wanted to.
Tiffanie可不是这么说的
That's not what tiffanie says.
你会被休学接受调查
There'll be an investigation. You'll be suspended.
你很可能会被开除
You could very well be expelled,
也许还要面临刑事指控
Maybe even face criminal charges.
Donnely夫人 请别这样
Mrs. Donnely, please don't.
Donnely夫人 别给我养母打电话
Mrs. Donnely, please don't call my foster mother.
我什么都告诉你
I'll tell you everything i know about this.
- 我已经都知道了 - 不 但是我还知道其他事
- I know all about it already. - No, but i know some other stuff,
像是谁在教师办公室里偷东西
Iike who been thieving from the teachers' lounge,
或者撬开体育馆的柜子
Or tagging gym lockers,
- 还有... - 请找Jeffries小姐
- or even... - miss jeffries, please.
- 请找Jeffries小姐... - 我是Tilghman高中的Donnelly夫人
- Miss donnelly, please... - This is mrs. Donnelly calling from tilghman middle.
请听我说 我知道
Listen... i know...
你还记得扎Philmont先生轮胎的人么 我知道谁干的
Remember, the boy who cut mr. Philmont's tires? I know who did that.
我知道一起谋杀
I know about a murder.
是真的
I do.
我们选出部分我们认为可以从
We've identified certain students
这个特殊课程和小班教学中
We feel will benefit from the special curriculum
受益的学生
And the smaller class size.
我们从8年级里挑了10个学生
We've chosen 10 students from the eighth grade
参加到这个项目中
To participate in this program.
被选中就要去?
You get chose, you got to go?
- 没错 - 如果你不想去呢?
- That's right. - What if you don't wanna?
是强制性的
It's mandatory.
我们认为这个项目能够使所有人受益
We feel that this program will benefit everyone.
你们会得到关注
You'll get the attention you need.
那我们不再被其他人干了
And we outta everybody else' shit.
对不起 是被欺负
My bad. I ain't mean to curse.
不过你说的对
Yeah, but you're right, though.
你们被分出来了 靠你们自己了
This class get tore up, it's only on y'all.
- 那我们不在原来班里了 - 这也是一个班级
- So we get put outta class. - This is a classroom, too.
你们在座的所有人都反复被证明
And every one of you has proven time and again
不适合常规的班级教育
That you're not ready for a regular classroom.
但是这是个新项目 如果你们努力
But this is a new program that if you work it
- 会让你们做好准备(继续上学) - 准备进监狱吧
- Is going to make you ready. - Ready for gen pop.
这就是个监狱 我们被他妈的孤立了
This is prison, yo. And we in solitary an' shit.
- 注意言辞 - 孤立
- Word. - Solitary.
你说得好 孩子
That's good, son.
就是要孤立
This is solitary.
你们就呆在这里了
This is the hole up in here.
他是个好孩子 真的
He's a good kid. He really is.
你一旦打了这个电话 他的名字就会进入系统了
And once you make that call, his name's gonna be in the system.
我有什么办法? 他说他知道一起谋杀
What can i do? He says he knows about a murder.
我必须通知警方
I have to notify police on this.
至少让我给信得过的人打个电话
At least let me call someone i trust.
就是他
That's him right there.
准备好 你不去?
Stand by. You don't wanna be in on the collar?
不了 如果你去 他会认为这只是禁毒行动
Nah. If you take it, he'll think it's a straight interdiction,
我会在保释审查时再给他来个惊喜
And i get to surprise him at the bail review.
先生女士们晚上好 请注意
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. Can i have your attention?
现在抵达D号门第四站台的
Now boarding at gate letter d, track 4,
是来自纽约 经停BWI机场火车站
The southbound 8:45 acela express
和华盛顿联合车站
from new york, Making station stops at bwl rail station
8点45分南行的Acela特快列车
And union station, washington.
妹子 帮你拿包吧?
Sister, help you with your bag?
- 不用 谢谢 - 不要害怕
- No, thank you. - Don't be afraid.
害怕什么? 你是谁?
What should i be afraid? Who are you?
只是送你到门口
Just walk you to the door.
- 我丈夫在外面等我 - 真想见见他
- My husband is waiting outside. - Like to meet him.
我会和你一起 确保你安全
I'll wait with you, make sure you're safe.
真的没这个必要
That really won't be necessary.
- 先生 我是Amtrak车站铁路警察 - 请你过来一下
- Amtrak police, sir. - Could you step over here please?
- 这是干嘛? - 把包给我
- What is this? - Give me the bag.
发生什么事?
What is going on?
我不认识他 你要带我去哪里?
I don't know this man. Where are you taking me?
- 他说了什么? - 没说太多
- What'd he say about it? - Nothing much.
毒品?
Drugs?
我没有问那么深入
I didn't question him too close.
一起谋杀
A murder.
- 我应该上报的 - 谁知道他到底知道多少?
- I should take it downtown. - Who knows what he really knows?
我只是 我不想他的名字进入系统
I just-- I don't want to see him get chewed up by the system.
让我试试把它结了
Let me try to keep this close,
把它交给一个会便宜行事的人
Give it to someone with a little bit of discretion.
非常感激
Appreciate it.
- Carver - Carver?
- Carver. - Carver?
Ellis有点远 我想他比较适合
Ellis has come a long way. I think he'd be right for this.
你为什么在意他? 他是你的什么人?
Why do you care? And what's this kid to you?
我不知道
I don't know.
他是我的学生
He's one of my students.
警长
Sergeant.
- 干净的 两个都是 - 你说什么?
- Clean. Both of 'em. - Say what?
那包里只有女人衣服
Nothing in that bag but ladies clothes.
他们身上都很干净
Nothing dirty on either one of 'em.
除非你有其他想法 不然我们得放了他们
Unless you got another idea, we gotta cut 'em loose.
他告诉我 他只是个中间人
From what he says, he was just a go-Between.
他传送信息
He delivered a message.
他告诉受害人在特定时间去特定地点
He told the victim to be at a certain place at a certain time.
那他怎么知道发生什么
Then how does he know:
他说大家都知道Lex是怎么回事
He says everyone knows what happened to lex.
这是街头规则
It's in the streets.
至于学校的那一件
This other thing at the school.
我发誓我没做 Anna小姐
I swear i didn't do it, miss anna.
我没有参与 你会知道的
I didn't do it. You'll see.
校方会进行调查那个 我们则调查这个
School's gonna look into that, we're gonna look into this.
只要Randy愿意合作 说实话
As long as randy cooperates, tells everybody the truth--
- 但是如果别人知道了... - 我明白
- But if word got out-- - Understand.
所以他要照常上学 不要乱说话
That's why he's gonna go to school, keep his mouth shut,
别惹事 规规矩矩
His nose clean, go about his business.
这孩子在这两件事上都犯了错
Child's shown such bad judgment in both instances.
我同意
Agreed.
但是我可以看出来 他不是个坏孩子
But from what i can tell, he's not a bad kid.
Dennis
Dennis:
你这么早要去哪?
Where you goin' at so early?
我去跑步 还有些工作要做
i'm gonna go run, and then i got lawn work later.
你会回来的吧?
You comin' back, right?
什么意思 什么我会回来?
What you mean am i comin' back?
你又要那样了么?
It's gonna be like that, huh?
你在说什么? 哪样啊?
What do you mean? Like what?
- 去哪? - 高地城
- Where to? - Highlandtown.
去你的根据地露下脸
Flush out yo' base, little trooper.
- 你好吗 Spider? - 嗨 小伙子
- What up, spider? - Hey, shorty.
谢谢 我知道怎么投票
Thank you, but i know how i'm voting.
我上班要迟到了
I'm gonna be late for work.
Anna小姐 你去投票的时候 我能在这里等你吗?
Miss anna, is it okay if i stand out here While you go vote?
- 哪都别去 知道吗 - 是的 女士
- Don't you go nowhere, boy. - Yes, ma'am.
怎么样 伙计?
So, what up, man?
他们给你多少钱做这个?
So, how much they payin' you for this?
他们说40 但是我要在这站一整天
They say like 40, but i gotta work the whole day though.
- 知道我说什么吧 - Spider
- Know what i mean: - Yo, spider.
那个是Spider吧?
Yo, that was spider, right?
- 是的 - 他要去哪?
- Yeah. - Well, where'd he go?
谢谢 但是我不能投票
No, thank you, man. I can't vote.
有犯罪记录? 重罪?
Conviction? Felony?
- 走开吧 兄弟 - 好吧 兄弟
- Move on, man. - A'ight, man.
你再见到Spider 告诉他来我的健身房找我
You see spider again, you tell him he need to come past my gym.
他几个星期没出现了 我们需要谈谈 好吧?
He ain't been round in weeks, and we need to talk. A'ight?
好的
A'ight.
- 大一点的孩子们哪去了? - 我不知道
- Where's the older kid? - I don't know.
好吧 就你了 把这些发到每个人手上
Okay. You're hired. Shove one of those into every hand you can.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
- 你今天怎么不去学校? - 今天不用上学
- Why you ain't at school? - Ain't no school today.
- 犹太节日? - 选举日
- One them jew holidays? - Election.
- 那你要干嘛? - 不知道 出去玩
- So what you gonna do? - Dunno. Hang.
记得我说过你要站出来吗?
What'd i say about steppin' up?
Brianna断了我们的粮 我们要自谋生路
Brianna turn off the faucet. We gotta make some rain.
我先换衣服 我们去找Bodie
I'm gonna get dressed. We go see bodie.
孩子 我有其他事要你做
Kid, i got something else for you.
把这些发到高速公路和Winchester路之间的每家每户
Put one of these in every door Between the expressway and winchester,
从Freemont大街到Fulton大街
And from freemont to fulton.
你可以自己去也可以找几个朋友一起
You can do it by yourself or you can get some friends,
我今天下午会过去看看 检查一下
But i'm gonna come past this afternoon, make sure it's done.
好的 每家每户 没问题
Okay. One in each door. Cool.
这是你今天的报酬
This is for the day's work.
这是你的跑腿费 但是别搞砸了
That's your walk-Around. But don't you fail me.
- 用了一整天才投完票 - 什么回事 孩子?
- Took forever. - What's all this, son?
他说如果我把这些传单发出去 我有钱拿
Man said if i put these fliers in doors, i can get paid.
- 我发完就马上回家 - 必须的
- I come right home after. - You right you will.
别在街上乱跑
You ain't in these streets no more.
是的 女士
No, ma'am.
听起来她是认真的
Sounds like she mean it.
11点的新闻?
"11 :00 news," huh?
闭嘴
Shut up.
我之所以在这里傻站着 都是因为你搞的那出
I'm on this shit detail Because you wanted to stir the pot.
明天 如果我们公布Braddock一案
And tomorrow, if we bust open the braddock case,
- 才没人会关心 - 机不可失啊
- Nobody's gonna give a fuck. - Life is timing.
废话 搅屎棍
No shit, fucknuts.
Tommy Carcetti 你好吗?
Tommy carcetti. How you doing?
- 他很可爱 - 谢谢
- He's a cute one. - Thanks.
Tommy Carcetti 你今天投票了吗
Hey, tommy carcetti. Hope you're voting today.
投了
I am.
你投给谁了? 给点提示吧
Well, who's it gonna be? Give me a hint. Come on.
别让我想东想西了
Don't keep me in suspense.
- 你不用担心我的票 - 非常感谢
- You don't have to worry about me. - Appreciate it.
Tommy Carcetti 正在竞选市长
Tommy carcetti, running for mayor.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet ya.
- 还要在这呆多久? - 我想我们可以走了
- How much longer? - I think we can wrap this up.
我们今天还有好几个地方要跑
We got a lot more places to be today.
Tommy Carcetti 我认识你爸
Tommy carcetti. I knew your dad.
第一区的民主党俱乐部
First district democratic club.
- 真的吗 - 我想说的是 我投了你一票
- No kidding. - Just wanted to say you got my vote.
- 谢谢你 - 他们本来有机会的 （巴尔的摩黑人为主）
- Thank you. - They had their chance.
- 瞧瞧现在这个城市变什么样了 - 我希望能改变这个现状
- Look what shape the city's in. - I'm hoping to turn things around.
- 无论如何 谢谢你的支持 - 我的意思是 你希望政客偷取利益
- Anyway, thanks for your support. - I mean, you expect politicians to steal.
- 我没有 事实上 - 这是游戏的一部分 我理解
- I don't, actually. - It's part of the game. I understand.
但是我们拿走三分之一 而不是三分之二
But we took one dollar outta every three, not two outta three,
不像那些黑瓜那样
Iike these moolies.
我的意思是 总要给城市剩下点
I mean, leave something for the city, for christ sake.
我说的对不? 祝你好运 议员
Am i right? Best of luck, councilman.
- 黑瓜? - 抱歉
- Moolies - Sorry.
竞选传单
Election fliers:
跑一下 丢进邮箱里
Yeah, just run up, stick 'em in mailboxes,
- 或者屏门之类的 你知道 - 空房子呢?
- You know, screen doors, whatever. - What about the vacants?
我们甚至不需要管空房子
We ain't even got to do the vacants.
狗屎 有些街区全是空房子
Shit. Some blocks ain't nothing but.
这就是我的意思 这钱来的容易
That's what i'm saying. This be easy money.
- 我不想做 - 我做 - 我也做
- Don't wanna do it - I do it. - Me too.
如果我们有辆车 会更容易
Yo, this shit'd be easier if we had a car.
别闹了 Anna小姐已经找我够多麻烦的了
Dang, donut. I'm in enough trouble with miss anna as is.
怎么样 Mike? 你来吗?
So, what up, mike? You in?
好吧 晚点聊
All right, then. I'll holla at you later, boy.
听我说 Namond的情况是这样 那个词怎么说来着?
Look, namond's been-- What's the word?
他不太稳定 有时候做得很好
He been inconsistent. You know sometimes he be doin' good,
- 后时候 他就-- - 我们谈过这事
- Then other times, he just-- - We talked about that.
他会做得更好的
He gonna do better.
是吗?
Ain't you?
选举日特惠 买二送二
Election day special, two for two!
- 我不知道 - 我可知道
- I don't know. - Oh, i do.
你要给点货这个孩子
You gonna give this boy his own package
要不然有你好看的
Or there gonna be some drama.
你要我和Wee-Bey说吗? 或者你想和他说
You want me to talk to wee-Bey? Maybe you wanna talk to him.
我给你他的号码 他有手机
I give you his number. He got a cellphone.
没必要这样 我超尊敬Bey的
All that's not even necessary. I got all the respect in the world for bey.
那向他的家人表示一下
Then show some for his family.
别让我失望 听见没有
Make me proud, hear?
该死 你妈真是头母老虎
Damn, boy. Your mama's what niggas call a dragon lady.
她不会吃人
She don't blink.
谁知道 招子给我放亮点
Yeah, gimme some insight, though.
- 干嘛? - 看看你是不是那么屌
- To what? - Why you is what you is.
怎么了 你们要去哪?
Yo. What up? Where y'all goin'?
饿死了 我要去吃东西
Hungry, man. I need to eat.
不 过来 活还没完
Nah, come one. Let's finish this.
- 不 这破事太闷了 - 你妹的
- Nah, yo. This shit is boring. - Fuck it.
听好了 如果你们不做完 我不会给钱的
Listen, i ain't even gonna pay y'all If you don't finish the job, so...
你已经拿到钱了?
you already got the money?
蠢货 如果那傻逼已经付钱了
Fool, if the motherfucker paid you out already,
那我们还在这里干什么?
Then why the hell are we still here?
因为这是工作
'Cause this is the job.
屁话 那家伙只能怪自己
Shit, the man ain't got nobody to blame but hisself.
先给钱是他的错
It's his fault for payin' up front.
赶快给我们发钱
Yo, you need to split that money up or something
别浪费时间
'Cause time is a-Wastin'.
活还没做完呢
Didn't even finish the day's work.
至少也给我来点吃的
Get me something at least.
- 鳟鱼 - 要汽水吗?
- Lake trout. - Soda too?
- 好 草莓味 - 没问题
- Yeah. Strawberry. - A'ight. I got ya.
他们去哪了?
Hey. Where the crew at?
Randy给他们找了点活干
Randy got 'em all some job
发竞选传单之类的
Handin' out election fliers or whatever.
你不去?
You ain't wanna do that?
不 太没劲了
Hell, no. It's bullshit, man.
- 我也有活干 - 什么?
- I got a job too. - Word?
Bodie给的 我搞了点货
Yeah, with bodie. I'm movin' the package.
你要和我一起吗?
You wanna go in on it with me?
真的? 我们可以一起搞
You sure? We could work together.
不了 那是你的活
Nah, man, that's your thing.
你自己去吧
Go do what you do.
好吧 回头见
Yeah, a'ight. I'm gonna holler at you.
她真不错 是吧?
She a cute one, ain't she?
小子 我爱妞儿
Yeah, boy. You know i love the women.
你见到Spider了吗?
Hey, you seen spider around any?
他快有一个月没出现过了
I mean, he ain't been 'round the gym in like a month, man.
我给他留口信 他不回我
I leave messages, he don't call.
我不懂这是什么回事 他可是我最好的拳手之一
I don't understand, man. He was one of my best welterweights.
他干嘛就这样溜了?
Now, why would he just quit like that?
你怎么不去问他妈?
Why don't you ask his moms?
原来这样 该死 我被关了好一会
Well, shit. I was locked up a good while, right.
我的意思是我不是什么好鸟
I mean i ain't no angel.
你不是
Naw. You ain't that.
大伙儿 谢谢
Thanks a lot, folks.
干得好 加油 我们快赢了
Good job. Keep it up. We're almost home.
你是最棒的
You're the best. The best.
竞争很激烈
Heavy turnout all around.
西边的情况可能对我们不利 我不知道--
Big lines on the west side might be bad for us. I dunno but--
我们正在西巴尔的摩
We're out here in west baltimore,
- 在他的根据地 - 这是今天的新闻?
- The heart of his political base. - This is today?
直播 现在就在Lafayette广场
This is live, right now in lafayette square.
Clay Davis刚刚宣布他全力支持Royce
Clay davis just said his whole organization Was out going door-To-Door for royce's ticket.
他又倒向市长那边了
So much for laying back on the mayor.
我们还给了这个鸟人2万元
We paid $20,000 for this shit?
他很可能去找Royce要了3万元 这贱逼
He probably went to royce and shook him down for another 30. Motherfucker.
Clay Davis一定是知道些我们不知道的事
Clay davis must know something we don't.
足以让他两头要钱
He knows just enough to get paid twice.
要怪只能怪我们先给钱了
Gotta blame ourselves for payin' this thief up front.
还是值得一试的
Hey, it was worth a shot.
市长助理们私下告诉我他们在担心...
Aides to the mayor have told me privately that they are concerned...
谢谢
thanks, yo.
我再拿支冻的
I'm-A get me a cold one.
双手放墙上站好
Grab the wall.
Walker警官
Officer walker.
我不会中你的圈套的
I ain't gonna be out here strapped.
你要打劫穷人吗?
Aw, you gonna take that on a humble?
小子 你不知道游戏规则
Boy, you don't know there's rules to this here game.
- 规则? - 是的
- Rules? - Yeah.
你的猎枪呢 Omar先生?
Where your shotgun at, mr. Omar?
你们是吃火药了吗? 我可没犯什么事
What is wrong with y'all, man? Y'all ain't got no charges here.
谋杀指控 该死的
Charge is murder, motherfucker.
谋杀 我杀谁了
Murder: who i kill?
你好吗 Omar
Hey, omar.
- Mcnulty 你们到底在搞什么? - 你来告诉我好了
- Mcnulty. What the hell goin' on here? - You tell me.
抢劫杀人 在杂货店里
We got a warrant for a robbery murder. In a store.
车来了
Wagon's here.
嗨 McNulty 我要打一个电话
Hey, yo, mcnulty, i need a phone, yo.
去你妹的电话
Fuck your phone.
你们要抓我的话 我要先打个电话
If i'm going to booking, i need to make a call tonight, yo.
410-958-6612
410-958-6612.
打吧
An' let it ring.
通了
Here.
Butchie 我被抓了
- Hey. - Yo, butchie. I'm locked up, yo.
你需要什么? 我可以保释你
What you need? I got your bail.
不用 他们说是谋杀
Nah, no bail. They sayin' it's murder.
谋杀? 别担心 知道了
Murder? Well, don't worry. I got ya.
你是民主党的还是怎么?
You some kinda democrat or what?
今天城市的竞选非常激烈
Voter turnout was heavy all day across the city
好几个选区今天一大早
With some precincts reporting lines
7点开始就排起了长队
As soon as the polls opened at 7:00 this morning.
但是竞选工作人员
Election officials, however,
报告说今天出现了几起事故
Reported few problems throughout the day.
现在投票结束了
Now the polls have closed,
竞选的工作人员
Officials at the board of elections downtown
开始了漫长的点票过程
Have begun the tedious process of tallying the vote,
今晚很可能是一个不眠之夜
Prepared for what could be a long night.
通过全市316个选区中的过半数统计得知
With just over half of the city's 316 precincts reporting,
议员Thomas j. Carcetti以2%的微弱优势领先
Councilman thomas j. Carcetti has a narrow lead of 2%.
根据以往经验 最后得出结果的
Traditionally, those precincts that report latest
那些选区都是来自西巴尔的摩
Tend to be from west baltimore,
那些地方都是挺市长Royce的
Which is expected to favor mayor royce in the late going.
- 怎么样? - 还好 没什么问题
- How it go? - Good. Nothin' to it.
我全指望你了 Nay
I'm countin' on you, nay.
早些时候在主选区的票站民调显示
Exit polls done earlier in the day in key precincts
投票者主要关注城市的几大热点
Show voters divided over the challenges facing this city,
例如犯罪和教育方面
Such as crime and education.
这场竞赛在过去几个星期里都僵持不下
Since this race tightened in the last couple of weeks,
我可以预测这次的竞选
I've been saying that this election
就像是地面作战
Would be won on the ground.
谁的野外作战能力强谁就赢
And whoever has the best field operations will take it.
投票决定一切
It's all about the turnout, and this is something--
Bond的情况怎么样?
What about bond?
好的 待会再和你说
All right. Talk to you in a few.
Bond给了Demper一下狠的
Bond's running really strong against demper.
看来我们会有一名新的州检察官了
Looks like we might have a new state's attorney.
这对你来说意味着什么?
What does that mean for you?
Demper是Royce的手下
Well, demper's royce's boy.
打起精神来 Tommy
Dare to get your hopes up, tommy.
这样吧? 我们出去透透气
You know what? Let's get outta here for awhile,
出去走走
Take a walk.
你死定了
I'll get your ass.
- 真美 - 发达的城市
- Pretty. - A little ripe.
是啊 可惜不能为港口的臭味做点什么
Well, can't do anything about the way the harbor smells.
人们会指望你做点什么
People are gonna expect you to.
我想也是
I guess.
- 你好像很有信心 - 我有预感
- You sound confident. - I have a feeling.
这个城市会再次繁华起来的
Could be a great city again.
创造一些就业机会
Pull some jobs in here.
人们会搬回来 房子会有人住
People move back, fix up the houses.
手机又响了
It's ringing again.
是Terri
Terri.
- 你应该接 - 我不需要每五分钟了解一次情况
- Maybe you should answer it. I don't need an update every five minutes.
- 我们应该回去了 - 就回去了?
- No, we should go anyway. - Do we have to?
我肯定他们现在慌了 找不到你在哪
I'm sure they're frantic. They don't know where you are.
什么事?
Yeah?
在和我妻子散步
Taking a walk with my wife.
马上回来
On our way.
Royce妥协了
Royce is conceding.
西边选区的结果出来了
The west side precincts came in
我们在其中一些选区得到了五分之二的票
And we pulled two outta five votes in some precincts.
我们抢了他的大本营
We stole his base.
我们赢了
We won.
这不是好消息吗?
Are we happy about that?
我想是的
I think so.
真是个好消息
I think we are.
是的
Yeah.
你肯定?
You sure?
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Please.
感谢你们的贡献和付出
I want to thank you all for your hard work and dedication.
为你们自己鼓掌 来吧
Give yourselves a hand. Come on.
我刚接到市长Royce和议员Gray的电话
I just got off the phone with mayor royce and councilman gray.
他们都很亲切 我请求他们的帮助
They were very gracious. I asked for their help.
我的意思是 我们还要赢得大选
I mean, we still have a general election to win.
巴尔的摩有没有共和党的候选人 我不知道 我不清楚
Is there a republican candidate For mayor in baltimore? I don't know. I'm not sure.
但是 就算我们赢了
But, assuming that we win, we still have--
要使城市变样 我们依然有很长的路要走
We still have a lot of work to do to turn this city around,
我需要你们每个人 愿意加入我们的每个人
And we need everyone-- Everyone who's willing to join us
为我们的后代 留下一个更好的巴尔的摩
In making a better baltimore for our children.
我不想发表什么长篇大论 相信我
I don't want to make a long speech. Believe me.
你们也不愿意听吧 我不想说太多
You don't want to hear it. I don't want to make a long speech,
我会逐个感谢你们每一个人
So i'll thank each of you individually.
但是今晚 就让我们好好庆祝一下
But for tonight, let's celebrate.
Tommy! Tommy!
- 你好吗? - 谢谢
- How you doin'? - Thanks. Hey.
Damond
Damond.
我期待和你一起共事 Mayor先生
I look forward to working with you, mr. Mayor.
我也是 也要恭喜你
Likewise. And congratulations to you, too.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 我要回家了 - 别这样 留下吧 不会太久的
- I'm going home. - No, come on. Stay. I won't be long.
会的 这是属于你的夜晚
Yeah, you will. It's your night.
Tommy Tommy
Tommy. Tommy.
看看是谁赢了
Look what washed up on the beach.
恭喜你 Mayor先生
Congratulations, mr. Mayor.
过来问个好 期待和你一起共事
Just came by to wish you well. Looking forward to working with you.
你还敢出现在我面前?
Shouldn't you be dead to me?
别那么说 我对你很好了 孩子
Sheee-It. I took it easy on you, son.
我本来可以要你两倍的代价
I coulda had you for twice as much.
你赢的太容易了
You got off cheap.
他说的对
He's right.
Butchie让我们来的
Butchie sent us.
你犯了什么事?
What you in for?
22-55条
I'm here on a 22-55.
我倒过来
I talked back.
- 黑瓜 - 黑瓜
- Moolie: - Moolie.
- 他在你面前这样说? - 事实上 他说的有道理
- He said that in front of you? - He made a point of it, in fact.
是你说我必须要保住自己的大本营
You're the one said i oughta shore up my base.
- 你没那么叫他? - 对民主的讽刺
- You didn't call him on it? - The ironies of democracy.
一票就是一票 我可不会丢回去不要
A vote's a vote. And i never throw one back.
说到选票 你有投我一票吗 Norman
Speaking of ballots, did you vote for me, norman?
投票的神圣性
The sanctity of the voting booth
是美国民主的基石之一
Is a cornerstone of american democracy.
- 我要走了 要送你一程吗? - 好啊
- I gotta go. You need a ride? - Yeah.
- 来 你是最棒的 - 谢谢你 Norman
- Come here. You're the best. - Thanks, norman.
- 休息几天吧 - 好的
- Yeah, take a break. - You got it.
- 一天 两天 - 来
- One day. Two days. - Come here, you.
- 保重 - 我会给你打电话的
- Be good. - I'm gonna call you.
我知道你会
I have a feeling you might.
晚安
Good night.
我也该走了
i should go, too.
再喝一杯?
One for the road?
当然
Sure.
- 苏格兰威士忌可以吗? - 当然
- Scotch okay? - Sure.
我必须承认 感觉太棒了
You know, i gotta admit, it feels good.
你应得的
You deserve it.
你那么努力
You worked hard.
说的没错
I did. I do.
- 干杯 - 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
我接受这份工作的时候 你答应过我赢了有奖励
You know, when i took this job, you promised me a win bonus.
那是你应得的
Well, you earned it.
我不能这么做 现在不能
I can't do this. Not now.
来嘛 Tommy
come on, tommy.
你一点都没变
You haven't changed.
我从Norman那听说
Hell, from what norman tells me,
你几乎为了一个金发小妞落选了
You nearly fell off the campaign trail for a blonde
两个月前在Stonewall的晚宴上
At the stonewall dinner two months ago.
他不得不把你拉出酒吧
He had to drag you out of the bar.
并不是我不想要--
It's not that i don't want to--
你现在是市长了 没错
you're feeling a bit mayoral. Right.
你现在上位了
You're onstage now.
Tommy...
Well, tommy...
四年对你来说可是很长的时间
four years is a long time for a fellow like you.
这也许是你我的最后一发了
This could be your last chance for a while.
你确定?
You sure?
也许你吸取了什么教训
Maybe you have learned something.
给我写张支票
Write me a check.